ABCs of Death 2 1/2 is a horror, thriller, comedy film directed by Joe Stas.
An anthology of 26 fan entries submitted for inclusion in ABCs of
Death 2, each offering various takes on the letter "M".
(segment "M is for Mobile"), played by Ali Arslan.
(segment "M is for Mobile"), played by İlker Arslan.
Best Friend (segment "M is for Mother"), played by Anastasia Baranova.
Victim (segment "M is for Manure"), played by Dani Barker.
Townspeople (segment "M is for Martyr"), played by John Beck.
Bret (segment "M is for Merry Christmas"), played by Beat Billson.
ABCs of Death 2 is a 2014 American comedy horror anthology
film produced by Ant Timpson and Tim League.
It contains 26 different shorts, each by different
directors spanning various countries.
It is a sequel to The ABCs of Death (2012), and second
installment in the ABCs of Death film series.
Directors featured include Jim Hosking, Lancelot Oduwa Imasuen, the Soska sisters, Julian Barratt, Rodney Ascher,
Kristina Buožytė, Larry Fessenden, Navot Papushado, Aharon Keshales, Bill Plympton, and Vincenzo Natali.
The film received a much more positive response than its predecessor.
A second sequel titled ABCs of Death 3: Teach Harder was announced to
be in development during the post-credits title card.
However, due to illegal pirating of the second film, the status
of the project has been left in development hell.
Despite this, producers released what they categorized as a
spin-off, titled ABC's of Death 2½ in 2016.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.